{
    "subject": "resource/Steven_Pinto-Borges",
    "predicate": "property/position",
    "object": "resource/Midfielder",
    "human_readable": "Steven Pinto-Borges plays the position of Midfielder.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9622641801834106,
            "question": "What position does Steven Pinto-Borges play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8647305965423584,
            "question": "What teams has Steven Pinto-Borges played for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7988144159317017,
            "question": "In what sport does Steven Pinto-Borges participate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7273004651069641,
            "question": "Is Steven Pinto-Borges a forward?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.619542121887207,
            "question": "Where did Steven Pinto-Borges learn to play this sport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5481865406036377,
            "question": "What role is typically associated with the position of Midfielder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47276896238327026,
            "question": "Has Steven Pinto-Borges won any awards or recognition for his playing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3520810902118683,
            "question": "Are there other positions besides Midfielder in this sport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23482629656791687,
            "question": "Can you name a famous Midfielder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14361447095870972,
            "question": "What are some of the skills required to be a successful Midfielder?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Steven Pinto-Borges plays the position of Midfielder.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5244_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a famous Midfielder?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5244_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there other positions besides Midfielder in this sport?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5244_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Steven Pinto-Borges won any awards or recognition for his playing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5244_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5244_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5244_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5244_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5244_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5244_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5244_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5244_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5244_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5244_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5244_44.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states that \"S. Pinto Borges is a 32-year-old, 70-rated Center Midfielder from Portugal\".  Center Midfielder is a type of Midfielder. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I found the following:\n\nThe triple in question is:\n\"Steven Pinto-Borges plays the position of Midfielder.\"\n\nAccording to the documents, S. Pinto Borges is indeed described as a \"Center Midfielder\". Therefore, the information supports the triple.\n\nHere's the JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"S. Pinto Borges is a 32-year-old, 70-rated Center Midfielder from Portugal,\" which supports the triple that Steven Pinto-Borges plays the position of Midfielder."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}